

# Prathmesh Tangade Android Development

prathameshtangade097@gmail.com 🔀

inkedin.com/in/prathmesh-tangade in

github.com/prathamesh10346

twitter.com/prathameshtang2

dev.to/prathamesh10346



# **ABOUT ME**

Im an independent and self-motivated undergraduate student in Savitribai Phule Pune University , specialization in Information & Technology, currently I am working on Flutter. I am always highly enthusiastic about my work and task's ahead

## **SKILLS**

- HTML CSS & Javascript
- C, C++, Python
- Java, Kotlin
- · Android, Flutter
- Team Leadership
- Communication Skills

## **HOBBIES & INTEREST**

- Content Creation
- Development & Design
- Bibliophile
- Stagecraft
- Football

## **EDUCATION**

### Bachelor of Engineering (B.E), Information Technology

JSPM's Bhivarabai Sawant Institute of Technology and Research, Pune. 2019 - Present

#### Senior Secondary (XII), Science

Sudhakar Naik College Arts & Science, Akola (H.S.C)

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Flutter Developer Intern FindUrFix

15/11/2022 - Present,

- · Managing the app and improving it
- 2 Month Internship

## **Android Developer Intern**

**OASIS INFOBYTE** 

01/08/2022 - 5/09/2022,

- Made some Project According to the Task
- 1 Month Internship

# **VOLUNTEERSHIP**

Technical Associate Lead at GDSC (2022-2023)

In our Campus there is a Club called Google Developer student Club in that club I am selected as an Technical associate lead

Creative Team member at MLSC(2022-2023)

In our Campus there is a Club called Microsoft Learning Student Club in that club I am selected as an Creative Team Member

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

COMPOSE CAMP FACILITATOR

In this camp I taught student about Kotlin & jetpack Compose

Google cloud Ready Program

Completed Ultimate milestone also get familiar with cloud

## **PROJECTS**

## **Bookmyshow**

I've made a really minimal and clean UI of the app using flutter and integrated it with JSON in the app.

#### **BMI Calculator**

I've built a app where you can calculate the BMI of a person by adjusting the values inside the app.

Also You can check my other project on my Portfolio in Project section https://prathamesh10346.github.io/portfolio\_PT/